Guide to the New York State AFL-CIO Records WAG.031
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Inventory, 1
  - Programs for Employment and Workplace Systems, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Project New Day, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Protectionism, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Prudential Insurance Co., undated (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Publications, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Public Advocate, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Public Citizen, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - NYS Public Employee Conference, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Public Policy Institute, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - NYS Public Employee Federation, 1994 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Public Relations, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Public Works, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Purdue Chicken Company, undated (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Puerto Rico, 1992-1995 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Pyron Corp., 1988 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Queens Botanical Gardens, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Queens College, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Radioactive Dumping, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - Radon Gas, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - A. Phillip Randolph Institute, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Reagononmic, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Rebuilding Americas Infrastructure, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Recent Development in the Law Affecting Labor Unions, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Recodification of Law Project, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Record Newsletter: Federal Election Commission, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Reebok, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Reform Concepts, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Rehabilitation, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Relay Newsletter: Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Renssaeler Polytechnic Institute, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Repeal Property Tax, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Replacement Workers, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - The Reporter Newsletter, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Republican National Committee, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - District 1199 RWDSU, 1987-1990 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Research Institute of America, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Brooklyn Navy Yard Resource, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Resolutions, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Resumes, undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Retirees Action Committee, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Retool New York Investment Plan, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Retool NY Master Plan for Transportation Statewide, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Revenue Recovery Services, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Rhode Island AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Right to Know Law, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Right to Work, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Right to Work Laws, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Riverfront Park Centre, Elmira NY, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute on Government, 1984-1989 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Rocky Mountain Building and Construction Trade Union, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Royce Hotel, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Rugmark Campaign, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Rural Opportunities, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Golden Ruscher, 1972-1984 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - St. Bonaventure University, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Raceway, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Sales Tax Refundable Credit, 1988-1991 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - MS Sass, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Safety and Health Committee, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Programs, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - School Apprenticeships, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - School to Work, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - NY School Construction, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - School Buildings, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - School Custodians, undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Schultheis and Pannettieri, 1985-1996 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Scweizer Aircraft, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Scouting Labor and Scouting, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Seafarers International Union, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Martin E. Segal and Company, Consultants and Actuaries, 1985-1992 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Security and Law Enforcement Employ Council 82, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Segai Company, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Sematech, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Seneca Falls Machine Company, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Senior Citizens Directory, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Senses: Rebuilding the Infrastructure of New York, 1987-1996 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Service Employees International Union, 1984-1993 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Service Employees International Union Local 32B-325, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - SEIU Local 74, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Sewage Treatment Plants, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Sexual Harassment, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Shared Union Systems, Inc., 1984 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Sheehan Associates, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Shipping Industry, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Simmons Machine Tool Co., 1989 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Sithe Energy, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Don Skarrup, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Small Business Advisory Board, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Smoking Regulations, 1986-1987 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Social Democrat, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Social Security, 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - SOS Bulletin, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Social Democrats-USA, 1990-1993 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - NYS Society of Public Accountants, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Solidarity Committee of the Capitol Distribution, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - The Socioeconomic Newsletter, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Breakfast for Soviet Delegation, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Soviet Union, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Spano, Nicholas, 1984 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Special Response Corp., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - 1984 Issue Special Wage Scale and Fringe Benefit Supplement (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - State Communities Aid Association, 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - National Conference on State Legislators, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - State University of New York, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Statewide Youth Advocacy, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - State of Israel, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - State of the State, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - State Labor Legislation Enacted 1986 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - State Ties, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Staten Island Naval Base, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Statue of Liberty-Ellis Island Campaign, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Statue of Liberty Centennial Celebration, 1985-1987 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Steamfitters Union, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Steuben Athletic Club, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Stewart Airport, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Strike/Laundry and Dry Cleaners, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Strike/St, Joe Resort, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Striker Replacement Bill, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Strokestown Park House, undated (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Committee on Economic Development, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee on Health Insurance, Council on Health Care Financing, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Visions: Friends of Mario Cuomo, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Vermont State Labor Council AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Vietnam Veterans Memorial, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Vocational Education, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Subcontractor News, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Sub-minimum Wage Program, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Subpoena, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Super Conducting Super Collider, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Superfund Amendments and Reauthorization Act of 1986 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - SUNY Stoney Brook Legislative Conference, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Sweatshops, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Syracuse Building Trades, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Syracuse Hotel, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Takeovers and Mergers, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Tap Letters, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Tax Cut and Budget: M. Cuomo, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Union Busting, undated (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Union Songs, undated (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Union Label of NYS, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Union Label Services Trades Department State AFL-CIO, 1985-1993 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Union Labor Life Insurance Company, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Independent Unions and Affiliated Unions, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Union Pension Funds, undated (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Union Membership and Earnings, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - NYS Department of Labor: Unemployment Insurance, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Unions Today: New Tactics to Tackle through Time, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - How Union Help Your Family, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - Unions for the Performing Arts, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - UF & CW Retail Food Store Employees, 1985-1990 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - United Nations, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - United Optical Workers Union, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - United Paperworkers International Union, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - United Steelworkers, 1982-1990 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - United Transportation Union, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - United University Professions, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - US Holocaust Memorial Museum, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - National Security Seminar: US Army War College, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - US Department of Commerce, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Justice Department United States, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - US Department Labor Apprenticeship, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - US Department of Education: Workplace Literacy Grant, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - US Department of Labor: Employment Standards Administrations, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - US Department of Labor: Raymond Cordelli, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - US Department of Labor: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - US Department of Health, Education and Welfare, SS Admin., 1974 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - US Department of Health and Human Services, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - US Office of Personal Management, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - US Information Agency, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Unity Coalition, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - US News and World Report, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Universal Badge and Label Co. (Union Made), undated (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - UDC Hearing on 42nd Street Redeveloping, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Utility Workers, 1988-1992 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Value Health, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Harry Van Arsdale Jr. High School Task Force, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - H. Van Arsdale Jr. Memorial Association, 1988-1993 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - C.T. Vogel and Co. Inc Insurance, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Video Display Terminal Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Voter Registration Month, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Volunteer the National Center, undated (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Wal-Mart, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Wage Reporting, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Adam Walsh Foundation, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Wards Island Water Pollution Control Plant, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Washington State AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Wayne State University, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, 1984-1990 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - The Power of Communications for Unions, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Uniformed Fire Officers Association, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - US Air, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Unite, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - United Bible Service, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - United Federation of Teachers, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - United Federation of College Teachers, 1992-1993 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - The Washington Spectator, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Water Meters, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Wee Care Day Care Center, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Foster Wheeler, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Western NY Council on OSHA, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Wicks, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Winsten, Richard, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Worker-Commitment on the Future of Management Relations, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Work Fare, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Workmens Circle, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Workers Comp, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Workers Comp, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Workers Comp, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Occupational Diseases Workers Compensation, 1984-1988 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - WC/VF Benefits Chart, undated (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - WC/VF/DB Highlights, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Women in Construction, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Water Pollution and Control Bill, NY & NJ, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - West Valley Demonstration Project, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Westway Project, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - White Lung Association, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Wilson House, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Winsten Richard: Apartment Lease in Albany, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Wisconsin State AFL-CIO, 1988 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Witteck, Marie, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Womens Legislative Project, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Womens Occupational Health and Resource Center, Columbia University, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Temporary State Commission on Workers Compensation and Disability Benefits, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Workers Compensation Law Taxicab Drivers, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Workers Defense League, Inc., 1984 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - World Federalist Association, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Workers Institute for Safety and Health, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Workmans Circle Home and Infirmary for the Dead, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - World ORT Union, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Workplace Rights, undated (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Work Zone Safety, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Workers Under Communism: The League for Industrial Democracy, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Workers Comp Occupational Diseases, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Workers Compensation and Unemployment Insurance Under State Laws, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Workers Compensation Board, State of NY: Newsletter, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Working Together, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Worker Memorial Day, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Yonkers Green, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Youth for Energy Independent Leadership Seminar, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.1-S.2692, 1979-1980 (Box 84)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.2706-S.6327, 1979-1980 (Box 85)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.6341-S.21023 / A.3A-A.1421A, 1979-1980 (Box 86)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: A.1439-A.12217, 1979-1980 (Box 87)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.73-S.3430, 1981-1982 (Box 88)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.3480-S.6958, 1981-1982 (Box 89)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7000-S.10511, 1981-1982 (Box 90)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: A.107A-A.13185, 1981-1982 (Box 91)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.112-S.3576, 1983 (Box 92)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.3759-S.21018 / A.3-A.8213, 1983-1984 (Box 93)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7-S.5512, 1984 (Box 94)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.5563-S.8478, 1984 (Box 95)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.8536-S.10057, 1984 (Box 96)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.1-S.1427, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.1456-S.2577, 1985 (Box 98)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.2554-S.3515, 1985 (Box 99)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.3522-S.4995, 1985 (Box 100)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.5061-S.6517, 1985 (Box 101)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.6547-S.7494, 1985-1986 (Box 102)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7502-S.8696, 1986 (Box 103)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.8787-S.9388, 1986 (Box 104)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.16-S.2063, 1987 (Box 105)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.2081-S.4481, 1987 (Box 106)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: A.5125-A.8030, 1987 (Box 107)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.4001-S.10592, 1987-1988 (Box 108)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.4618-S.6738, 1988 (Box 109)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.6740-S.7141, 1988 (Box 110)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7147-S.7286, 1988 (Box 111)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7311-S.7926, 1988 (Box 112)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7995-S.8299, 1988 (Box 113)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.8308-S.8914, 1988 (Box 114)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.8974-S.9188, 1988 (Box 115)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.9254-S.21020, 1988 (Box 116)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: A.8679-A.9547, 1988 (Box 117)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: A.10856-A.12038, 1988 (Box 118)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.16-S.948, 1989 (Box 119)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.969-S.1806, 1989 (Box 120)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.2018-S.2497, 1989 (Box 121)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.2498-S.3120, 1989 (Box 122)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.3124-S.3789, 1989 (Box 123)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.4126-S.4501, 1989 (Box 124)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.4559-S.5441, 1989 (Box 125)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.5485-S.6224, 1989 (Box 126)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7015-S.7241, 1990 (Box 127)
  - Legislative Files/Bills: S.7248-S.7297, 1990 (Box 128)
  - General Files: AFL-CIO News Inside Education; Vocational Education, 1970-1984 (Box 129)
  - General Files: Agency Rules Governors Approval Messages, 1979-1980 (Box 130)
  - General Files: Governors Appointments Workers Compensation, 1979-1981 (Box 131)
  - General Files: Kemp Niagara County Democrats, 1979-1981 (Box 132)
  - General Files: Labor Laws Legislative, 1980s (Box 133)
  - General Files: Actors Westway, 1981-1982 (Box 134)
  - General Files: Agency Rules & Regulations Full Value Assessment, 1981-1982 (Box 135)
  - General Files: Governors Program Bill Ways & Means Report, 1981-1982 (Box 136)
  - General Files: Apprenticeship Zimni Bill, 1983-1984 (Box 137)
  - General Files: Childrens Issues Labor Lobbyists, 1984 (Box 138)
  - General Files: Legislative Alert Reaganomics, 1984 (Box 139)
  - General Files: Rehabilitation ZAP Courier Service, 1984 (Box 140)
  - General Files: Budget Empire State Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 141)
  - General Files: Generic Drugs Toxic Torts, 1985-1987 (Box 142)
  - General Files: Federal Election Commission Record Invitations, 1985-1989 (Box 143)
  - General Files: Letters to Governor NY 10-13, 1985-1989 (Box 144)
  - General Files: OSHA Public Hearing Calendars Association, 1985-1989 (Box 145)
  - General Files: Retirement System Unemployment Insurance, 1985-1989 (Box 146)
  - General Files: Unemployment Insurance Workers Compensation, 1985-1989 (Box 147)
  - General Worker Files: Actors Equity Association United Food & Commercial Workers, 1979-1980 (Box 148)
  - General Worker Files: Ironworkers Unemployment Insurance, 1979-1980 (Box 149)
  - General Worker Files: Cemetery Workers State, County & Municipal Employees, 1981-1982 (Box 150)
  - General Worker Files: Actors Equity United Optical Workers Union, 1981-1983 (Box 151)
  - General Worker Files: Actors Equity Utility Workers, 1983-1984 (Box 152)
  - Contract Negotiations; Elections for collective bargaining representation; R.G.4-NY Metro Contract Negotiations, 1959-1973 (Box 153)
  - Plant Closings, 1960-1986 (Box 154)
  - Project agreements/plans; BCTC Letters, Casino Legislations, 1974-1983 (Box 155)
  - Bills & Legislative Programs, 1983-1984 (Box 156)
  - AFL-CIO Department & Committee Statements, 1984-1996 (Box 157)
  - Meeting Reports, 1985 (Box 158)
  - Committee & Council Meetings (Paul Cole), 1985-1986 (Box 159)
  - Convention Proceedings, 1986-1988 (Box 160)
  - General Councils & Committees: BCTD Jewish Labor, 1986-1989 (Box 161)
  - AFL-CIO & International Affairs Meetings & Conferences, 1986-1991 (Box 162)
  - AFL-CIO Labor Committee & Council Meetings, 1986-1995 (Box 163)
  - AFL-CIO Meeting Notes & Press Releases, 1986-1995 (Box 164)
  - Miscellaneous Files: Budget; Tony Burns; Governors Press Releases; Job Training Partnership Act; Labor Committee Report, 1987-1989 (Box 165)
  - AFL-CIO Councils, 1988-1992 (Box 166)
  - Convention & Meeting Reports, 1988-1994 (Box 167)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 168)
  - Press Releases; COORS, 1990s (Box 169)
  - Convention Files; Print Requests; Purchase Orders & Travel Requests, 1984-1991 (Box 170)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Materials, 1984-1988 (Box 171)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Materials; Executive Committee Minutes, 1985-1996 (Box 172)
  - Photographs: 23rd Constitutional Convention; Assorted Conventions; General Photographs and Contact Sheets, circa 1959-1982 (Box 173)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Videos: "Working People," episodes 85, 86, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 013, Cassette 1-2)
  - Robert F. Wagner press photos and portraits, 1945, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 011, Folder 2-3)
  - Photograph: 11th Annual Convention, 1950-10-05 (Box Shared Tamiment 017, Folder 5)
  - Local 371 Ephemera, 1992 (Box 173)
- Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; 4 websites in 4 archived websites.
  Scope and Content Note
  The New York State AFL-CIO, in 1958, is the federation of labor unions in New York State affiliated with the AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations). The website contains information on their legislative action campaigns, press releases, regional and state news, endorsements, council members and other councils, and event listings. Crawling of the website began in 2007.
  Also includes Union Strong, the podcast of the New York State AFL-CIO. It is published biweekly and focuses on issues facing union members and how being in a union benefits workers.
  The YouTube channel for the New York State AFL-CIO, dates back to 2007. Includes videos from their podcast Union Strong, convention speeches, and political action and endorsement videos.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  Websites were accrued semiannually. In 2020, https://unionstrong.podbean.com/ and https://nysaflcio.org/ were increased to biweekly. Crawling was decreased to monthly crawls in 2021.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of nysaflcio.org and podbean.com in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints. Facebook was blocked.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored with the permission of the content owner.
  Flipbook documents were captured, but unable to be played back in browser.